That logo music just gets you pumped.
Right?
I'm sorry. I just, I'm excited
to be here. It's been a while.
You know, for a long time,
I wasn't sure I'd ever be back.
Disney bought Fox...
there was a whole boring rights issue,
blabbity-blabbity-blah.
But then, it turned out, they wanted me.
The one guy
who shouldn't even have his own movie...
much less a franchise.
Marvel's so stupid.
Look, we know the title of this thing. So...
I know what you're wondering.
How are we gonna do this
without dishonoring Logan's memory?
And I'll tell you how.
We're not.
I'm gonna let you in on a little secret.
Wolverine is not dead.
Sure, it made for a perfect ending
to a very sad story.
But that's not how
regenerative healing factors work.
You think I wanna be out here
in beautiful downtown North Dakota...
digging up the one and only Wolverine?
No, thank you.
But the fate of my entire world is at stake.
He may not be living his best life,
but he sure as hell ain't dead.
Bingo.
Yahtzee.
Yes, yes, yes.
Damn it!
Son of a bitch!
You...
Christ. Motherfucker!
My world is fuck...
That was weird.
I'm much calmer now.
Look, I'm not a man of science.
But you seem incredibly passed away.
But it's good to see ya.
I gotta be honest,
I've always wanted to ride with you, Log.
You and me getting into it.
Deadpool and Wolverine just fuckin' shit up.
Can you imagine the fun, the chaos...
the residuals?
"G'day, mate.
"There's nothing that'll
bring me back to life faster...
"than a big bag of Marvel cash."
Me too, Hugh.
But, no. No, no, no.
You had to get all noble and die for real.
Goddamn it!
I could really use your help right now.
Wait!
I'm warning you, I'm not alone.
Wade Winston Wilson...
you are under arrest
by the Time Variance Authority...
for too many crimes to list.
Come out...
and we'll extend you the courtesy...
- of taking you in one piece.
- Death by day-player.
Last chance.
Throw out your weapons
and come out peacefully.
I'm not gonna give you my weapons...
but I promise not to use them.
There are two hundred and six bones
in the human body.
Two hundred and seven
if I'm watching Gossip Girl.
Here we go. Maximum effort.
Okay, peanut.
Guess we're getting that team up after all.
Maradona from outside the box!
Goal!
Come on, big fella.
I am soaking wet right now.
To be clear, I'm not proud of any of this.
The wanton violence,
the whiff of necrophilia. It isn't who I am.
It isn't who I wanna be.
Who I wanna be?
Well, to help you understand that...
I've gotta take you back.
A little joyride I took
through space and time...
to the day that changed everything.
I can't believe I'm finally here.
I've waited for this moment for so long.
Thank you, sir, for seeing me.
I firmly believe...
that my services could be of...
great use to your organization.
Now I know...
I was caught smashturbating
in the lobby of Stark Tower...
- but I can assure you that...
- Smashturbating?
I'm sorry, what, what was that?
No, I'm sorry.
That, that's when you get those toy...
Hulk hands, right? And then you just,
you look down, and you just...
you brace yourself,
and you ravage the midsection.
- Pinch the... Yeah. Okay.
- I get it. Okay, thank you.
- The picture's painted.
- You get the gist.
What exactly brings you here today?
Why am I... Wow. Okay.
I care.
I know I turn everything into a joke,
but I...
I care, and I, I wanna use that feeling...
for something important.
I, I wanna matter.
I need to show my girl that I matter.
And...
you know,
I feel like I'm wasting the good stuff here.
- Is the man not gonna be joining us?
- The man?
Yeah. I should save this if he's gonna...
As, as far as you're concerned right now,
I'm the man.
- No.
- The man is me.
I am the man in this circumstance.
He doesn't do this kind of thing anymore.
- Cameos?
- Meetings.
- Entry-level meetings.
Entry-level?
Aren't you the chauffeur...
- maybe?
- I... Common misconception.
- Okay.
- I did begin my career as Mr. Stark's driver.
- Quickly pivoted to...
- Chauffeur.
- ...the Head of Security.
The Head of... Of course, yes, yes, yes.
And why I am vetting your résumé.
You seem to have left out
whether or not you had...
any experience as a member of a team.
Could you maybe
add a little bit of perspective there?
No, yes, of course. I was Special Forces...
- Okay.
- but I was... Mainly, I was team leader...
founder, really, of X-Force.
Sadly, they,
they all perished in action though.
How exactly did that happen?
Well, the police say gravity, but if...
Just between us...
- they didn't test well in the focus group.
- I see.
- Particularly Cable.
- X-Force.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Look,
I can see this isn't going well.
Please stop writing. Look, I, I...
I'm just... I wanna be an Avenger.
I wanna be an Avenger.
Why do you wanna be an Avenger?
Look around you. I mean, they're the,
they're the best of the best.
And, and what they do matters.
I need to be an Avenger.
Sir, my girl has kinda had it with my shtick,
and I, if I don't, you know...
turn things around
and do something with my gifts...
I don't think it's gonna
really work out for me...
and I wouldn't blame her.
Avengers are a very unique group
of superheroes...
that stand for something...
more than just fighting and wearing costumes.
I mean, people look up to us.
Kids look up to us.
- They...
- I'm sorry. "Us?"
I wasn't aware that you were an Avenger.
- Avengers-adjacent, technically.
- Oh, wow.
What's your superpower?
Is it parallel parking? I am so sorry.
That was cruel.
I lash out when I'm nervous.
Won't happen again.
- Let's cut to the chase.
- Please.
You just said moments ago...
that you wanted to be an Avenger
because you need it.
Yes, sir, I do.
But the Avengers don't do the job because
they need it.
They do the job because people need them.
Do you see the distinction?
Yes, sir.
Please, Mr. Hogan.
I don't wanna spend the rest of my life
like an annoying one-trick pony.
All right.
Oh, my God, you're standing.
Yeah, now's the time that we stand.
Damn it.
Now, the problem might be that you're...
reaching a little, little too high.
Aim for the middle, and you'll never miss.
Right? I think you got a good heart.
I believe what you're saying.
But not everybody's the world-saving type.
I'm not, and I'm happy.
Right? I found my place.
Find your place.
- All right? Get back out there.
- Mm-hmm.
- We'll keep an eye on you. Good luck.
- Okay.
Fetch the car. I wanna hit Shake Shack.
Rejection makes me hungy.
- Really? No?
- No, no. Please.
- Yeah, no, no, no. Okay, thank you.
- Oh, okay.
You know what they say.
When one door closes...
your locker at work opens.
Now let's go sell some certified
pre-owned vehicles, motherfu...
Technically, the,
the Carnival's not a minivan.
It's an MPV.
So how does the Kia compare to...
- the Honda Odyssey?
- The Odyssey?
That's a great question.
It doesn't fucking suck.
You know, you can answer
the question without swearing.
I'm sorry, Tammy, I don't, I don't have kids.
Not that I haven't dreamt of that...
but I don't have a lot of vaginal sex.
You'll get 'em next time, pal.
And look,
you can always go back to superhero-ing.
I mean,
I know I'd like to see you back in the suit.
I don't keep it in my locker
so that I can wear it.
I keep it in my locker in case
we need to saddle up again.
Hey, hey, hey. What?
What is that doing in there?
I'm done.
And I'm fine with being done.
Look, is sales the best match?
Probably not.
Is this the life that
I always imagined for myself? Fuck no.
But this is the right fit for me,
Sugar Bear, it is.
Okay, Mr. Wilson.
I'm just saying, once a month,
we could go on a little mission.
We're human beings. We crave purpose.
After all, we're Deadpool.
Please stop saying that. We're not Deadpool.
I'm not even Deadpool anymore.
Well, if you're gonna have a midlife crisis,
go big.
A few years ago...
a friend of mine got his nipples pierced
with a titanium chain...
that goes down
and attaches to his Van Johnson.
Are, are you feeling grumplestiltskin
'cause it's your birthday?
What?
No.
Surprise!
Hey, you guys are lucky I'm not armed.
Get in here.
If this were six years ago,
you'd all be dead.
So then, he gets out of the cab,
and you will not believe it.
- I turn around, and what do I find?
- AirPods.
- His AirPods. Come on.
- His AirPods!
Crazy story.
- Every time. Come on.
- Every single time.
Make any sales today?
You know I didn't.
Did you sell any dreamcatchers on Etsy
or whatever it is that you do?
Our rent's due in three days, Wade.
I can't keep carrying you.
Relax. I have the money.
I sold some old blood pressure medication
I found lying around.
You tryin' to kill me, motherfucker?
I'm not the one dousing everything in salt, motherfucker.
I pray every day that...
fire finds your body...
and finishes the job...
- God didn't have the nuts to do.
- That's hurtful.
If you could hear the look on my face,
you'd smell how sad I am.
You watched anything good?
Great British Bake Off.
Oh, goddamn.
That show stood between me and suicide
for ten years.
Those are my feelings
on abortion, religious freedom...
animal rights, privacy rights, vaccines...
free-market capitalism,
global climate change.
Yeah, duh-duh-duh.
No, no speaking lines, Buck.
Hi, Yukio.
Hi, Wade.
Nice fake o'clock shadow.
It's a summer balayage. From the French.
It's meant to mimic the
natural highlights of the sun.
- It's a toupée.
- It's a hair system.
- I love your hair system, Wade.
- Thank you.
Wanna do some cocaine?
Hey, cocaine is the one thing
that Feige said is off limits.
- What about Bolivian marching powder?
- They know all the slang terms.
They have a list.
- Even snowboarding?
- Even disco dust.
- White girl interrupted?
- Even Forrest Bump.
- Booger sugar?
- I wouldn't even try powdered gonuts.
- You wanna build a snowman?
- Yes. But I can't.
Pull here.
- Here?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
- That's the fun part.
Thanks for coming.
Yeah.
How's work?
Oh, I got a promotion.
No way.
Yeah. It's mind-numbing middle management,
but I'm happy.
That's great.
- You seeing anyone?
- How about you?
Yeah.
A guy from work. Dermot.
Dermot.
- He's kind.
- Good.
Likes to go hiking.
Hasn't gotten me shot yet.
Well, it's early days.
What about you? You seeing anyone?
No, no, I live in a one-bedroom apartment.
I share a bed with Blind Al.
- Okay. All right.
- All right.
Happy birthday to you
- Speech! Speech!
- Yes!
All right. Okay, okay, okay.
Birthdays.
Boy, every spin around the moon
is a new adventure indeed.
- Sun, dumbass.
- Okay, round-earther.
- Where was I?
- The adventure of life.
Right.
It's been a challenging few years.
Haven't seen you guys in a while.
Been through a lot, change of life.
- Menopause?
- Bitch, are you improv-ing?
- Mm-mm.
- Sorry.
I'm sorry that you had to see that, Yukio.
It's okay.
But I'm happy.
You know, and that's, that's...
because of each and every one of you.
I guess, what I'm trying to say is...
how proud I am, how grateful I am...
to be standing in a room...
with every single person I love.
I'm the luckiest man alive.
Make a wish, buddy.
Ten-four, good buddy.
Going down.
Wade Wilson?
Oh, yeah. Dancers.
Dopinder must have ordered you.
Are those supposed to be cop costumes?
Never mind.
Take your clothes off but leave the helmets.
And this isn't Pretty Woman.
We're kissing. All right?
What song do you guys normally dance to?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Is that supposed to be scary?
Pegging isn't new for me, friendo.
But it is for Disney.
Ah, ta, ta, ta!
Okay, I've never been a natural bottom,
so we're gonna take things real slow.
And I want some crazy eye contact.
Not you.
You.
Can't see your eyes through the mask,
but I can feel them.
We're gonna move on down the hallway...
so we can spare a cleanup on aisle asshole.
How does everyone feel about this plan?
- I don't like you.
- Yes. Let's hold on to that attitude.
And we're gonna do it angry.
Mr. Wilson...
you appear to have soiled yourself
while unconscious.
I wasn't unconscious. Who are you?
I go by the name of Paradox.
Mr. Paradox.
And you're sitting here at the TVA.
The Time Variance Authority.
We're really a watchdog organization...
except we're more lighthearted
than that sounds with a sort of...
throwback, ironic twist.
And we're in charge of defending
what's known as the Sacred Timeline.
Holy fuck. That is a shit-ton of exposition
for a threequel.
Is this because I used Cable's time machine?
Brought a couple of people back to life,
then I destroyed it.
- That was a long time ago.
- Yes...
we're aware of your abuse of your timeline.
And you were so abusive of it.
No, it has nothing to do with that.
Walk with me.
I brought you here, Mr. Wilson,
to tell you that you're special.
In fact,
you've been chosen for a higher purpose...
a purpose unclear even to me.
But one that could...
save the entire Sacred Timeline...
from a possibly grisly fate
sometime in the future...
which may very well need to be... avenged.
This Sacred Timeline...
I assume I'm going to marvel...
at how...
cinematic it feels?
Gratuitous cameos...
indiscriminate use of Variants,
the whole package?
Well, you tell me.
Cap!
You are no longer lost, Wade.
You can be a hero among heroes.
We've been surveilling you for quite a while.
- Subway station.
- A TVA outpost, yes.
- And what is that?
- Hmm?
Is that me? Is that Thor?
Is he crying?
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
That happens in the distant future.
- Why is Thor crying? Quick! Tell me.
- Do not speak to her.
Stop that. Eyes on me.
I brought you here
to offer you an opportunity.
The opportunity you sought years ago,
but for which you were not ready.
We believe you're ready now.
Ready for a chance to leave your timeline...
and join the greatest universe of all.
I am about to give you the thing
you've always wanted.
Oh, I smell what you're steppin' in.
The power in the Marvel Universe
is about to change forever.
I am the Messiah...
I am...
Marvel Jesus.
Can you excuse me for just a moment?
I'm just gonna go over here.
Suck it, Fox!
I'm going to Disneyland.
Get fucked!
- Where do I sign?
- Oh, there's no need for paperwork.
Good. Not to brag, but I do not read.
- Oh.
- There is one thing I will need, though.
Oh, fuck off!
Adorn me, Beardo.
Fuckin' A!
It's perfect! FYI...
your tailor is a predator,
but I love it. Snug.
No camel toe.
New car smell and adamantium katanas?
You shouldn't have.
Go ahead. Take it in.
And yes, your underwear is getting tighter.
That guy knows what I'm talking about.
His clothes says middle management...
but his eyes say fuck-y fuck-y.
Yes. You look very nice.
"Nice?" Your buddy here is ready to
throw it all away for me.
- You callin' your wife?
- HR.
Does your wife work in HR?
I'm really glad you're taking this so well.
Oh. I'm taking it well.
I have never had a problem
traveling for work. That said...
we should talk vacation days.
I'm more of a
one-week-on-one-week-off kind of guy.
I think it's what they do in Denmark.
You know, you'll never see a
Danish flag on the moon, but...
goddamn it, they're happy.
Now, let's power up your little
Amazon Fire phone there...
and zip me back home so I can let my friends
know that they've been upgraded...
to disciples.
Yeah. I don't think you... quite understand.
You will not be returning to your home
because there will be no home to return to.
Come again?
This time in my ears.
This is your universe, Mr. Wilson.
That...
is what happens when a universe
loses their Anchor Being.
See how it decays from the inside?
- This is how a reality dies.
- What's an Anchor Being?
An Anchor Being is an entity of
such vital importance that when they die...
their whole world
slowly withers out of existence.
You've just won the lottery
because I didn't die.
It was just a little midlife crisis.
I'm better now.
Oh, no, no, no.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, I love to laugh.
Can you imagine if you were the Anchor Being?
- Yeah.
- No, it isn't you, Mr. Wilson.
Your Anchor Being died
in an act of self-sacrifice so epic...
that it sent shivers down the Timeline.
I am referring, of course, to...
Logan. The Wolverine.
Don't be what they made you.
So this is what it feels like...
Logan.
Of course.
Logan?
The guy with forks for hands?
That Wolverine?
Yeah, I got it. You can turn your retro
graphics of death off now. Make it stop.
We're not doing it, Mr. Wilson.
We certainly can't stop it.
How long have we got?
In most cases, couple thousand years.
- Well, sweet.
- Well, most cases aren't fast enough.
Not for me.
What does that mean?
It means that I have been tasked...
with overseeing the end of your universe.
And regardless of what the
pencil pushers upstairs would prefer...
I will not...
waste my life watching it die slowly
of natural causes.
We used to just prune these things. Simple.
Elegant. Efficient. But I'm told the TVA...
doesn't like to do that anymore.
Well I do.
And no matter what my so-called
superiors say, the multiverse...
does not need a babysitter.
We need a mercy killer.
And in this instance...
I am the mercy killer.
What in the MacGuffin is that?
That's a Time Ripper, Mr. Wilson.
An accelerant.
Once completed, it will allow me to destroy
the spacetime matrix of your universe.
You see, I don't want to work for the TVA.
I want to be the TVA.
And the first step involves
showing this organization...
how much more efficient it can become.
To wit, I will be giving your universe
a swift and compassionate end.
And don't worry,
your friends won't feel a thing.
It'll be over just like this.
"Oh, what's that?"
Trust me.
You're gonna Old Yeller my fucking universe?
Mm... In your parlance, yes.
Two in the heart, one in the head.
Look, Mr. Wilson, you have two choices.
You can either rejoin your loved ones
and collectively cease to exist in...
I'd say, seventy-two hours. Or...
you join the Sacred Timeline.
And you end your days of
insignificance...
and mediocrity.
Wade.
Wade, you can finally...
finally, matter.
That's all I've ever really wanted.
I know.
And you know I'm,
I'm nothing if not morally flexible.
Yep, yep.
I'll do it.
Wise choice.
The Sacred Timeline's happy to have you.
I was actually talking about
finding the Wolverine...
and breaking your fucking nose.
Find him. Find him!
And boy, did he ever.
Which brings us back to this.
The desecration of the sacred corpse.
Oh, my God!
Oh! My own fucking arm!
Now we're talkin'!
Not like this!
No, dear God! No!
I'm sorry! Wolverine-ing is hard!
Make it stop!
Mangold tried.
You sick fuck!
Logan was a hero.
And the only thing worth a shit
to ever come out of Canada.
Get my country's name
out of your fuckin' mouth.
And my sword. Give me that.
Oh, I gotta find me another Logan.
An alive one.
Don't get up, guys. I'll see myself out.
Logan!
I'm gonna need you to come with me.
Who's asking?
Oh, look at this little Hairy Lou Retton.
Did you stick the landing, little guy?
Yes, you did!
Comic accurate short king.
Such a cute wittle Wolvie.
Cue the fuckin' montage, baby.
Ahoy! Everything seems to be on fire.
You have a dragon?
You have Anchor Being written all over...
Patch!
Now we're talkin'.
Oh, yeah.
That's the whole goddamn package right there.
Howdy!
I'm just... I'm auditioning Anchor Beings.
Oh. Yeah, that's gonna need some coconut oil.
What in the fuck?
Are you okay?
Oh, yes, yes.
Classic John Byrne brown and tan.
Now, you fought the Hulk in this outfit. No?
I'm Marvel Jesus, you dull creature,
and I will not...
It's not you. We're just going
in a different direction.
You know, from behind,
you look a little bit like Henry...
Oh, my fuck!
The Cavillrine. The legends are true.
And may I say, sir,
on behalf of all humanity...
this just feels right.
We will treat you so much better
than those shit fucks down the street.
You were just leavin'.
No, sir.
Not while the fate of my universe is at...
This one looks promising.
Down you go.
Again.
I told you. You're not welcome here.
You're not welcome anywhere.
Now get the fuck out of my bar.
Just give me one more drink
and then I'll leave.
That's not how it works.
It does now. Leave the bottle.
I know you, bub?
Nope. But I know you.
Everybody knows me.
I'm the Wolverine.
Yes, you are.
And I'm gonna need you
to come with me right now.
Look, lady, I'm not interested.
- Really gettin' into your cups here.
- Why would I go with you?
Because, unfortunately...
I need you...
and even more unfortunately,
my entire world needs you.
You two gonna fuck or fight?
You gonna take that from him?
Yep.
I can tell you have a sort of...
don't-get-too-close-I'll-only-
break-your-heart vibe going here...
but every other Wolverine
would've really hurt me by now.
And, I'm sort of on the tick-tick.
So upsy-daisy. Here we go.
- Whoa, whoa. Hey, hey!
- Up you go. I got you, big guy.
Whiskey dick of the claws.
- It's quite common in Wolverines over forty.
- You don't want this.
You're right. I don't.
And you don't want this.
Unless you wanna take a deep breath
through your fuckin' forehead...
I suggest you reconsider.
Let's go, peanut.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Watch this.
All right. That... Whoa.
Easy.
Good God.
Thirsty little honey badger, aren't ya?
It's okay. Keep goin'.
Audiences are accustomed to long run times.
Guess you'll have to do.
Okay, here we...
Oh! Look at those jammies.
That only took twenty fucking years.
One Anchor Being coming right up!
On your left, baby girl.
This Logan has the same
he-can-do-anything-even-musicals look.
And bonus...
he's actually wearing a costume...
like he's not embarrassed to be in
a superhero movie for once.
I don't understand.
You said my universe is dying...
because this sack of nuts
got himself killed.
- Well, problem solved.
- My God.
You actually think
you can replace an Anchor Being...
with this?
I wouldn't have accepted any other Wolverine
BT dubs. But you...
have outdone yourself
and brought me the worst Wolverine!
What do you mean, the worst one?
Mr. Wilson.
This Wolverine let down his entire world.
He's the stuff of legend,
but not in a good way.
And what he did...
well...
some things are just beyond forgiveness.
Okay.
How do I... How do I make this right?
I'll do anything.
I gave you a chance at greatness.
Because my superiors deemed you special.
Clearly not special in a good way.
Apparently you have some
important future purpose to serve.
With Thor. He holds me.
But, I did my duty.
I gave you the opportunity to be somebody.
And instead of accepting my offering
with humility and gratitude...
you broke my nose.
- It looks great.
- And you decimated dozens of my men...
with the exhumed corpse of a hero.
Dishonoring not only his remains
but his memory.
What are you, the Internet?
Your world is dying!
Thank you very much.
And there's no stopping it.
The humane thing to do...
is to make it quick.
Is the thought of vaporizing my universe
making you peckish?
I'm eating my feelings.
I'm about to lose everything that I've
ever cared about because that hairy...
thundercunt from down undercunt...
finally dies
and he's standing right behind me, isn't he?
Welcome to the MCU, by the way.
You're joining at a bit of a low point.
As for you, I wanna talk to your boss.
I want you to get him on the phone
and you tell him, her, or them...
that Marvel H. Christ isn't playing.
Holy shit.
I just heard a symphony
of buttholes clenching all at once.
You're off grid.
Your bosses don't know what you sick fucks
are doing down here.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I have a black belt in Karen...
And I'm gonna go upstairs...
and I'm gonna tell 'em all about
you and your...
Silence is nice, isn't it?
Where the fuck did he go?
To the trash heap. You'll fit right in.
That was close.
Don't just stand there, you ape.
Give me a hand up.
Nope. I'm actually okay.
Thank you very much...
Where the hell are we?
I don't know. Looks kind of Mad Max-y.
But that would be IP infringement, right?
Fucking jokes.
Fuck! Fuck.
Were you even listening back there?
If we don't make it back to that
Mr. Paradox asshole...
everyone I know is gonna die.
Not my fuckin' problem.
Oh, is that all you got?
Is that what you said
when your world went to shit?
Come again?
Yeah, I heard all about you.
How you screwed up everything.
You should be thankin' me
for pulling you out of that bed you shit in.
You back-stabbing son of a bitch!
Are you ready to be calm now?
Rest in pieces, Fox.
I don't want to fight you, peanut.
Doesn't matter what you did.
I just need your help.
I don't fuckin' care.
Uh-oh.
Fuck. This is gonna hurt.
All right.
Fuck it.
Let's give the people what they came for.
Let's fuckin' go.
Get your special sock out, nerds.
It's gonna get good.
Gotcha!
Baby Knife!
Let's see you grow your fuckin' head back.
Wait, wait, wait! I can fix it! I can fix it.
- Fix what?
- Whatever it is that you did.
Whatever made you so bad.
Those, those pricks in the TVA.
You heard him.
They have the power to end my universe...
but they also have the power to change yours.
We get back there...
and we can fix your world. Together.
I promise.
They can fix it.
Hey!
We fight each other, we lose.
Dear God, it's him.
- Who?
- The one.
The superhero equivalent
to comfort food, or Molly.
White guys' answer to all the
disappointments. And another A-lister.
Fair warning, gorgeous.
You're going to encounter
some indelicate language...
a smidge of ass play,
but we've been prohibited...
from using cocaine. On camera.
They're coming.
Who's "they?"
Oh, they're driving angry.
Now that's a superhero landing.
I got this.
Stay close.
Aye, aye, Cap'n.
You got this.
Cassandra is gonna be giddy
when she sees what we caught.
You can't run.
Everybody knows that.
You see anyone runnin', dick for brains?
You're not gonna love what happens next.
Oh. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God, he's gonna say it.
- Ah! Fuck.
- Oh, my God! He's gonna say it!
- Say what?
Avengers, assemble...
- Flame on!
- I'm sorry, what now?
Fuck!
We don't know that guy.
We thought we did.
I know you.
Holy...
Sabretooth.
Your brother.
Ready to die?
Wait, wait, wait!
Time!
You look ridiculous.
People have waited decades for this fight.
It's not gonna be easy.
Baby Knife.
Shoot the double, you take him down.
Side control, then full mount...
and you ground and pound
till he makes no sound because he's dead.
Shut the fuck up!
Oh, my God!
Okay. Good luck. I'm a huge fan.
What is it, girl?
Is there trouble at the well?
Big trouble.
Behold!
The head of your precious queen...
Furiosa!
I have the Wolverine!
I alone control her!
You come for me...
you come for her.
So sorry. I know it's pronounced "him."
I'm gender blind. It's my cross to bear.
Who's next?
Toad!
You're up.
- Uh-oh. Oh, holy...
- Fuck.
God of Thunder.
How long was I asleep?
Not all of you was asleep.
Don't bother.
They're very thorough.
If you know where we are, start talking.
You're in The Void.
Think of it as purgatory.
Reed called it a metaphysical junkyard.
Where anything useless goes
before it gets annihilated forever.
And where the TVA sends people that don't
play nice with the rest of the multiverse.
- Like you?
- And you.
What does the annihilating?
Alioth.
Alioth is in this thing?
From Loki, season one, episode five?
Everyone here is on the run from Alioth.
Most don't make it.
There's a resistance, though.
Other people like us that managed to survive.
They're hidin' out in the borderlands,
trying to find a way the fuck outta here.
Then that's where we go.
"We?" Us? A team?
The answer is yes.
Shake on it.
Fuck! You nicked it.
Just got the tip with
your little steak knife.
These "others" can help us
get back to the TVA.
Make 'em fix things.
Something funny, bub?
She might have somethin' to say about that.
Who's "she?"
In The Void...
you're either food for Alioth...
or you work for her.
Huh. Paul Rudd finally aged.
You must be this year's Juggernaut.
- Thank you.
- I'd keep your voices down.
She don't like the chatter.
She's gonna love you.
Is it... Is that Charles?
Hey... Hey, Chuck! It's us!
That's not Chuck.
Ah, shit.
Oh, ableism. Great.
That's not gonna go over well
with the woke mob.
A Wolverine.
I wondered when I'd get one of you.
You're one of Xavier's.
You-You know him? You know Chuck?
Oh, I knew him.
We shared a womb.
Tried to strangle the sly little fellow
with my umbilical cord.
Amen. I've never loved roommates.
Mine's blind.
Except she can see cocaine.
For some... reason.
You want to chime in, Your Majesty?
I'm dying here.
Who are you?
Charles Xavier's twin, Cassandra Nova.
- Bullshit!
- I was an anal birth.
You two are cute.
I have a good feeling about this.
And I've been trying to catch...
this little firefly for years.
Haven't I, Johnny?
Aw... You picked the wrong time
to make new friends.
Oh, Johnny told us all about you.
- Maybe shut up now.
- Yeah, maybe don't...
We're just talkin' here.
Yeah, Johnny told us
you're a psychotic megalomaniacal asshole.
His words, not mine.
Hellbent on domination and pain.
- You said all that about me?
- No!
- No! I don't... I didn't say any of that!
- Sticks and stones, Johnny!
Don't let her intimidate you.
It's like you said in the convoy.
This finger-lickin' dead-inside
pixie slab of...
third rate dime-store nut-milk...
can eat your delicious cinnamon ring...
- and kick rocks all the way to bald hell.
- Okay.
I have never said any of those words...
- in my entire life!
- Ha! The modesty.
People think I'm a shit talker.
But this guy...
Next level.
What? This... I... We...
I don't even know what half of that means!
- This... I... What? This...
- My hat's off to you, sir. Truly.
I didn't... He's... That's...
I don't...
Not my favorite Chris.
You stupid piece of shit.
You just got him fucking killed!
Hey! We're all grieving!
PS, do you know what
he was doing to the budget?
Alioth is hungry.
There's been some kind of mistake.
Big yellow is a back up Anchor Being...
and I'm Marvel Jesus. MJ, if you're nasty.
This may be hard to hear...
but there's another British villain
who's gonna destroy my universe...
and I'm gonna stop him.
Oh, honey, you don't really strike me as
the world-saving type.
Did I hit a nerve?
I didn't want it to come to this.
Either you help us...
or my friend here is gonna sing
the entire second act of Music Man...
with zero warm-up.
Where'd you get the chair?
Well, once in a while,
I do get a Charles through here.
Never mine, though.
No. He didn't care to find me.
Gen Z and their trauma-bragging!
Can't you just stuff it down,
turn it into accomplishment...
or cancer like the rest of us?
But I'm not like the rest of you.
Except maybe the Wolverine.
Now, we could be truly terrifying together.
You're that scary, huh?
The TVA certainly thought so.
They sent me here before I could walk.
And you know, it's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I love it here.
You live in a garbage dump.
I think we both know who lives
in the garbage dump.
The Void is a paradise.
I can wield my power here without shame.
Unfortunately I had no Charles Xavier
to teach me temperance.
What about your Charles?
Did he protect you?
Did he make you feel safe?
We're mutants. We're never safe.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I don't... I don't want the smoke.
I don't have any beef with you.
I just want to save my friends.
I just... I want to go home.
Well, the thing is, I could get you home.
- Good.
- But I don't want to.
Not good.
What do you want, Wade Wilson?
Your... fingers are inside me,
but not in a good way.
My brother could
enter one's mind with a thought.
I have to get my hands dirty.
I've got you.
I've got you...
What do you mean?
I can't, I can't reach you. You're not here.
I'm right here.
- No, you're not. I can't...
- I'm right here.
Then show me. You got to do something.
Show you what?
Show me you care about
something bigger than you.
Ever since they turned you down,
you took a knee.
Baby, you never got back up.
I know you're going through something.
Let me go through it with you.
- Your crazy matches my crazy.
Where'd you go?
Oh, my God.
You just say it. Okay?
Say, "I don't want you.
"I don't want to be with you."
Go ahead. Say it. Say, say, "I don't..."
Say it. You don't wanna be with me.
Tell me that and I'll walk away.
Say, "I don't want you."
Fuck...
You'll never fucking matter.
What?
- You'll never fucking matter.
- Fucking matter.
- You'll...
- never...
- fucking...
- matter.
- matter...
She never said that.
No.
But I bet she thought it.
You are so mean!
My brain could taste your fingers,
and they tasted like hate!
And where in God's name
is the intimacy coordinator?
You're so lost, Mr. Wilson.
And long before you came here.
This is Baby Knife.
She's gonna fuck you in the face now.
If you want to kill me,
it's going to take more than a little blade.
How about six?
My boy's wicked strong.
That's my big boy.
Yes, you are.
Well, this has been fun.
But the big guy needs to eat
and the rent is due.
By the way...
you're the rent.
Come on! Fuck!
You comin' or what?
Coming!
What you thinkin' 'bout?
Get the fuck off of me!
Almost done.
Almost done what?
Getting my knife out of your buttocks,
pervert!
Fuck!
Get your mind out of my pants!
I'm telling Blake.
New rules.
I talk now.
- That's gonna be very hard on the audience.
- Shut the fuck up!
Let me fuckin' think.
Now we gotta get back to Paradox, right?
Right?
- Am I allowed to speak now or...
- Just nod, asshole.
Right.
Then we find the others that poor kid, Johnny
was talking about before you got him killed!
"Poor kid." He's like fifty!
Yeah, if there's a chance they know
how to get out of here, we find 'em.
And make those TVA fuckers fix my shit
like you fucking promised!
I smell quest.
I smell food.
So what made you finally wear an
honest-to-God costume?
Mine's red so they can't see me bleed.
But I could see how
yellow would be useful too.
Have you been checked for ADHD?
Mm-mm.
But I've had several STDs, which...
were probably caused by ADHD.
Fuck!
What are you looking for?
Thank fuck.
No, no, no. That's rubbing alcohol.
You don't want to drink...
Oh, yeah. There you go. Fuck that liver.
Good. Okay.
What the fuck are those?
Back in civilian life, I wear a toupee,
but nobody knows.
Everybody knows.
Wanna talk about what's haunting you, or...
should we wait for a third act flashback?
Go fuck yourself.
You know...
in my world, you're...
You're well regarded.
Yeah, well, not in mine.
- They don't like me much in mine either.
- You don't say.
I wanted to be something, you know. I...
Shit, I wanted to be an Avenger.
- Fuck the Avengers.
- Yeah.
I didn't make the cut, though.
Same with the X-Men...
When my girlfriend left me...
- and then I just...
- You had a girlfriend?
Yeah.
Vanessa.
When we met, she was a dancer.
We had a whole life.
It was good.
But, oh, boy, I just...
Fucked that right up.
But you.
You were an X-Man.
Fuck that. You were the X-Man. You...
The Wolverine.
He was a hero in my world.
Yeah, well...
he ain't shit in mine.
You said, "Logan was a hero."
What happened?
He died.
How?
Well, technically,
you were chest-fucked by a tree, but...
really, you just ran out of batteries
trying to save someone.
Who?
The shitheels that grew her in a lab
called her "X-23." But...
she was just a kid.
A younger, daintier,
somehow meaner version of you.
You died trying to save her.
It was beautiful.
Look, mijo, I know you're hurtin'.
My blind, elderly, African-American roommate,
Blind Al, always says that...
pain teaches us who we are.
Sometimes we need to listen to that pain
instead of running from it.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah, she's wise.
No, no, no. That's her name?
You call her "Blind Al?"
Well, she's blind.
Look at you!
She's coming with us.
- No, she's not. Fuck no!
- Oh, yes, she is.
- Oh, yes...
- Sorry!
Sorry about that!
Come here, girl!
Who are you?
Oh, I'm Deadpool.
And I guess you're Deadpool too.
But in here, everybody calls me "Nicepool."
Oh, my goodness. Wait till you see Ladypool.
She is gorgeous.
She just had a baby too. And...
Can't even tell.
I don't think you're supposed to say that.
That's okay.
I identify as a feminist.
Right.
Are those gold-plated,
...50 caliber Desert Eagle pistoleros?
'Course.
To match my ear huggie.
Can I have 'em?
Over my dead body.
You're fun.
And I guess you've already met Mary Puppins.
AKA Dogpool.
Careful where you put your hands.
She's ninety percent g-spot,
and she'll let you know it.
You let this little flirt out of your sight
for one second and...
she starts shopping for a new papa.
If you can't be a responsible pet owner, then
maybe you don't deserve this little unicorn.
Guilty on all charges, Your Honor.
Shan't happen again.
Why are you so nice?
Oh, it costs nothing to be kind.
Shutting the fuck up is also free.
This is Logan.
He's usually shirtless,
but he's let himself go since the divorce.
Where's your mask?
Come on, guys.
Ugh, this guy.
We're looking for a group of survivors.
Oh, they're out there.
Yeah, but merc to merc, you better hope
that you don't run into the Deadpool corps.
Yeah, they're crazy.
They will chop you up into a thousand pieces
and hide you all over The Void.
If they could only process
their childhood trauma...
they'd go on one heck of a healing journey.
Look, we're headed for the borderlands.
You know where it is?
Yeah, that... That's twelve klicks due west.
I can lend you my ride, if you like.
It would be my honor.
No, no, no. Absolutely not.
Uh-uh. What the...
No! No!
Just get in the car.
This isn't a car.
This is a Honda fuckin' Odyssey.
Throttle response sucks a cock.
Dated infotainment system.
When Honda saw that untreated chlamydia
was makin' a comeback...
they invented the Honda Odyssey to compete.
Get in the fucking car.
She'll get you there safe and sound.
Old Betsy always does.
You're gonna have to
give me my dog back, though.
I know. Listen. Yes, child.
If you ever wanna give her up,
or if she needs a new home...
or if something
should happen to you...
I'd love to be her papa.
What would ever happen to me?
Lots of stuff.
- Jesus.
- No! We're running away.
- Give me that.
- The corn was too dense, girl!
- There.
- Come here!
- Fuck!
- Hello!
Bye.
Okay, I'm just gonna ask...
What's with the suit?
First thing I did when I flamed out...
- I took mine off.
- Drop it.
It's not that ugly.
- Stop talking about my suit.
- Did you make it yourself?
- Been there.
- Quit. Now.
The X-Men make you wear it?
Those sons of fuckin' bitches.
They are not your friends,
I'll tell you that.
Friends don't let friends...
leave the house lookin' like they
fight crime for the Los Angeles Rams.
Shut the fuck up about this, or...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Watch your frown lines, angel baby.
- I'm just trying to bond a little bit.
- Yeah, well, then talk about somethin' else.
Fine.
Stop it.
If they can fix your world...
what's the first thing you're gonna do
when you get out of here?
Get some rubbing alcohol shots,
maybe a wiper fluid chaser?
What did you say?
I said when you get back,
what's the first thing you're gonna do?
No, no, no. Before that.
If... they can fix your world?
What do you mean, "if?"
- I mean...
- You lied to me.
You don't have a fucking clue
if they can help me fix things, do you?
No. I, I mean...
Fuck! Fuck! I didn't lie!
- You lied!
- No! I made an educated wish!
Because I need you.
This. This is why. Right here.
'Cause if we don't do something, they die.
I don't know anything about saving worlds.
And why would I even care?
Because my entire world
is right here in this picture.
It's only nine people...
and I have no idea how to save it alone.
I know how to fuck people up for money.
But you...
you know how to save 'em!
At least the other Wolverine did.
Fuck! I guess I'm stuck with the worst one.
Did you say you made...
an educated fucking wish?
They call me "The Merc with the Mouth."
They don't call me "Truthful Timmy,
the Blowjob Queen of Saskatoon."
One more word.
Please give me one.
Gubernatorial.
Oh, fuck!
You know what? You're a fucking joke.
No wonder the Avengers didn't take you.
Or the X-Men.
And they'll take fucking anyone.
I mean, you are...
a ridiculous, immature, half-wit moron.
I have never met...
a sadder...
more attention-starved,
jabbering little prick...
in my entire life. And that says a lot,
'cause I've been alive...
for more than two hundred fuckin' years,
and I'll tell you...
that bald chick was right about one thing.
You will never save the world!
You couldn't even save a relationship...
with a goddamn stripper!
And motherfucker,
I wish I could say you'd die alone...
but it's one of God's best jokes
that you can't die...
except that's on all of us!
Oh, you got nothing to say, Mouth?
I'm gonna fight you now.
Oh, are you?
Mm. Not talkin' now, are ya?
You dirty bitch.
Whoo!
No, no, no!
Baby Knife!
I take it all back.
The Honda Odyssey fucks hard.
Too bad you don't, needle dick.
Oh, we're just gettin' started, bub.
Oh, you... Fuck!
Thor!
Where are we?
No clue, but... I like it here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay.
Look at you... all. You must be the others.
Terrific.
So just to refresh, you are...
- Wonder... Elektra? Yes. Who could forget?
- Elektra.
And you. I was not expecting to see you here.
I thought you were, you know...
retired.
Retarded?
"Retired."
I'm already in The Void.
I'm not trying to get canceled again.
I don't like you.
You never did.
And who's this succulent reminder
of my own inadequacies?
Look at you.
You look like the
superhero version of Hawkeye.
The name's Remy LeBeau, Le Diable Blanc.
But you can call me the Gambit.
It's been a while since I've seen
Sling Blade. Hit me again.
They call me the Gambit.
Do they? Are you sure you didn't just
really, really want them to...
but it never quite worked out?
You know,
we never had a Wolverine up in here.
But I can tell you now,
it's just a common courtesy to ask...
before you drink up all of my liquor.
Well, it's a good thing I don't give a fuck.
Fuck.
So embarrassing.
Well, now that that's settled, look,
we came a long way to find you three.
There's four of us.
There's four... Hey, wait. Is it Magneto?
Dear sweet God in heaven,
let it be Magneto...
- because with him...
- He's dead.
Fuck!
Now Disney gets cheap?
It's like Pinocchio jammed his face in my ass
and started lying like crazy.
Ooh, you nasty!
Not a single word. What do you do exactly?
Charge the playing cards
and make 'em go boom!
Your power's close up magic. That's good.
We're not totally fucked at all.
So who brought us here?
That would be me.
Don't make me regret it.
Holy shit. Logan. That's her.
That's X-23.
She's the one I told you about.
Hey, how did you all get stuck in The Void?
There was a knock at the door.
- TVA sent me here.
- Me, too.
Well, maybe I was born here.
It's, it's hard to know for sure.
TVA decided our universe was dying.
And I never even got a chance
to fight for it.
People like us don't go quietly.
TVA knows that, so they took us out.
The answer is yes. I'm in.
- In what?
- A team.
Me, you, you, and me. All of us together.
Let's get the fuck out of this place.
- Don't listen to him. He's a fucking liar!
- It was an educated wish!
Look.
We've been inside Cassandra's lair.
The only way out of The Void
is through her.
She can get us home. She told us.
Wait a minute, you've been inside?
- And you made it out alive?
- Bullshit.
- Nobody's ever done that.
- We did.
Every time one of us
has gone up against her...
they die.
The Punisher, The Quicksilver, The Daredevil.
Daredevil? I'm so sorry.
- It's fine.
- Okay.
Even that sweet, baby angel, Johnny Storm.
He up and gone missing like...
what, two days ago?
Ugh. That's so sad.
Wherever this Johnny fella is,
I'm sure he's thriving.
Look, there's, there's strength in numbers.
All right? Us...
plus, you guys. We can put Cassandra...
over our knee and force her
to let us out of The Void.
I know what it means to feel self-doubt.
- I don't feel that at all.
- I'm good.
Gnawing at your gut like a coked-up tapeworm.
It's like you're
holding up a mirror to my soul.
You guys may not have been able to
save your universes.
But you can avenge them.
It's what Johnny would have wanted.
Wait. You knew Johnny?
Oh, yeah.
Dickhead here talked him into a team up...
and Johnny came down
with a little case of the deads.
No, no, no. We don't know that.
It was just a flesh wound.
He may have survived.
If he survived that, he is prayin' for death.
- Thank you, Doctor Wolverine!
- Spill it!
What'd you do to Johnny, huh?
Talk or I'm gonna start dealin'.
Okay. Okay. Hey, hey, hey.
Look.
He ran his fat-ass mouth about Cassandra.
Then she zip-zapped his skin...
leaving his organs to
splash crudely onto the ground...
while the soil greedily drank his blood.
It was horrible.
He was like a brother to me.
Look, he died
before he could make a difference. But...
Look, maybe you couldn't save your worlds,
but...
but Jesus Christ, you can save mine!
I don't give a shit about your world, but...
if these two made it out of there alive,
maybe together...
we can get back in.
And take her down.
Where I come from,
we call that suicide, Chère.
If we can block her psychic powers,
we can get a leg up. I know it.
Now I know Magneto's dead.
But I'd venture to guess that his helmet...
- is lying around here somewhere...
- Cassandra melted the helmet.
- Fuck!
- After she killed him.
Fuck!
She don't play.
She knows that helmet was the only way
to protect anyone from her powers.
The only other helmet that strong is
Juggernaut's, but...
- he works for Cassandra.
- Juggernaut's helmet. That's it.
Yeah, and we done be knowing
that lid ain't comin' off...
- without that dome gonna come off wit'it.
- I'm so sorry, beautiful.
I want this to be gentle.
Who is your dialect coach? The Minions?
I feel like
we are missing critical exposition here.
I'm sick of this shit.
I'm sick of hiding.
Let's face it, our worlds forgot about us.
Or never learned about us.
The heroes we were.
Lives we saved.
Or wanted to save.
Maybe these two are our chance.
To be remembered.
The way we deserve.
Yes.
An ending.
- Legacy.
- Yes!
Yes! Let this man cook.
This is what I'm talking about.
Big slow-motion fights, sad music.
Everybody working together. Who knows if you
live or die? That sorta thing.
- Who's ready?
- I was born ready.
Yes!
Gambit?
I ain't know my daddy,
but I'm sure I shot out of his dick ready.
Jesus Christ, that is graphic.
Yeah. He was layin' them buttery nuts
all up in my mama...
and I shot out there and I said,
"What's up, Doc?"
Johnny must have loved you.
X-23, what's it gonna be?
The name's Laura.
- Let's fucking go.
- Let's fucking go!
- It's on like chicken and corn.
- Yeah!
- We're doing this.
- You're all fuckin' dead.
My God! Read the room.
Hey, hey. I'm not lookin' for company.
Get out of here.
You remind me of him.
Angry. Drunk. Mean...
- Sounds like a great guy...
- Wasn't finished.
Showed up when it mattered the most.
Couldn't help it.
You might not know it, but...
you're a good man, Logan.
You might not know it, but apparently,
I'm the worst Logan.
I got to have a life because of you.
I got to grow up because of you.
A lot of kids did.
A lot of kids didn't grow up because of me.
Trust me, kid, I'm no hero.
That suit says different.
Yeah. Do you like it?
Scott used to beg me to wear it.
So did Jean, Storm, Beast.
All of them.
They wanted me to be part of the team,
but I wouldn't.
Told 'em they all look fucking ridiculous.
I mean...
I couldn't have 'em thinkin'
I wanted to be there.
And then one day, while I was off on my own,
the humans came...
and went mutant hunting.
I can guess the rest.
No, no, let me...
Let me say it. I...
I need to say it.
By the time I stumbled home
shitfaced from the bar, it was too late.
They were dead. Every...
This suit's all I got to remind me of
who they were.
And what I did.
We're headed to Cassandra's at sunup.
Have fun. Not my fight.
We won't pull this off without you.
Hey. Whoever you think I am,
you got the wrong guy.
You were always the wrong guy.
What?
Alioth didn't get them.
Cassandra wanted to
play with them herself first.
They got away.
- Did they find the others?
- No.
Good. All right. Phew.
The others found them.
Oh, very cute. Well done, Pyro.
Classic bait and switch.
- You really got me there.
- Relax.
If they come after Nova, she'll handle it.
Cassandra is a lunatic wild card.
Why do you think we put her there
in the first place?
Thank God she's never chosen
to leave The Void.
The Time Ripper is hours away
from completion.
I cannot take any chances.
Well, maybe not.
But I can.
For a price.
Why do you have to
say it in that silly voice?
It's so icky.
You want it done or not?
All right. Your price.
Take her out.
Ugh. Mutants.
Ooh! Look at that there!
You see them biggum hands come closed.
Ain't not a wonna gettin' up inside there.
I think what Gambit's
trying to say is...
getting Juggernaut's helmet
ain't gonna be easy.
I'm just making stuff up at this...
- Yeah. Tilt up to Blade.
- Gun!
Where'd he get that little beauty?
That's Punisher's AT4.
Which Punisher?
There's been like five of them.
There's only been one Blade...
and there's only ever gonna be one Blade.
Incoming!
Ooh, this is gonna be good.
You know how long I've been waiting for this?
Whoo!
I'm about to make a name for myself here.
I don't think you guys walk away from this.
You just make sure
people know what happened here today.
And when you get out of here,
you have a drink for me, yeah?
You just stay on our six and get inside.
We'll make sure you get the package.
And we'll get our ending.
And boom!
Some motherfuckers still trying
to ice skate uphill.
You two escaping, I could live with.
But coming back? Willingly?
Boys are so silly.
I just need to get home.
Well, that's not on the menu, I'm afraid.
It's death or enslavement.
À la carte, of course.
Upsy-daisy.
Finally...
it's nice to give someone else
a chance to talk.
Not my strong suit.
You shouldn't have done that.
You are an interesting one, aren't you?
I do feel like
you get lost behind all of his...
Deadpools are
a dime a dozen here in The Void.
But you...
What's going on in here?
Interesting...
Not what I expected back here.
Behind the anger.
You're hiding.
From them.
From all the ones you let down.
So much pain.
I walked away.
They called after me and I...
I always do.
- Logan!
- I know.
That's not all you did.
Is it?
You found them.
The X-Men.
Dead.
Piled like wood.
What did you do?
I started killing.
And I couldn't stop. I didn't wanna stop.
All those bad men.
It's not just the bad ones.
My little animal.
And I turned the whole world
against the X-Men.
Blade!
Just once...
I wanna be the man
that Charles thought I was.
Logan...
in The Void you can be what you are.
I just wanna be free.
I can set you free.
I can silence all those voices.
I've got you.
No.
I got you.
Get it off!
You're gonna send us home,
or I'm gonna twist your fucking head off.
Why are you laughing?
I can't send you home
unless you get this thing off my head.
And as soon as you do that...
I'm going to boil your brains
on an atomic level whilst...
flicking my bean to the Enya box set.
There's an Enya box set?
Either you kill me...
or I kill you.
Both wonderful options.
You want me to do it?
No, I'll do it.
I have her neck right here.
It's really no problem.
You'll screw it up.
Oh, come on, Mr. PG-13,
except the last one!
What the fuck?
You have no idea what it's like!
Day after day. Shovel the shit.
Fetch the meats.
I have spent my entire...
Not everyone gets a speech.
She's gonna die.
Okay. Hey, hey. If I take this helmet off...
- do you promise you won't kill us?
- Fuck!
I promise...
I will kill you first thing.
Why are you like this?
I wish I knew.
Take it off.
- What?
- Take it off.
- Why?
- Just take it off.
- This is our only chance to fix our shit!
- Take it off!
I am wearing this suit.
And that means a lot of things,
but most of all...
it means I'm an X-Man.
And I know your brother.
As much as I want to fucking kill you...
every bone in my body
wants to fucking kill you...
he would not let me stand here
and watch you die!
Take your hands off.
This is for him.
This is for Charles.
Hey, no, no, no!
Don't you dare do me like Johnny!
My brother loved you.
He loved all of us.
Must be nice.
He would've loved you, too.
If he knew about you...
if he knew where you were...
he would've torn a hole in the fucking
universe to bring you home.
This is my home.
Well, then at least let us save his.
You want to hear something crazy?
An amateur magician
rolled through here a while back.
I killed him, of course.
Wore his skin around for four days.
But...
I found this...
little trinket...
on his lovely fingers.
Strange!
- Marvel sparkle circle.
- What is that?
This is your way home.
I do owe you for saving my life.
But let's keep things interesting.
I'd say you have about four seconds
before you're Alioth's food.
Race ya.
And as I said
we've got a standard three-year...
bumper to bumper warranty.
Glad you gave us a second chance.
And don't worry. Wade and I are a team,
so I'll see he gets half the commission...
That feels like a Kia.
It's a fucking Kia Carnival, isn't it?
Holy shit. That's Deadpool.
And that's Wolverine.
You're damn straight it is.
Fox killed him.
Disney brought him back. They're going
to make him do this 'til he's 90.
Let's go.
I'll clock you out!
Forever!
Forever.
Wakey-wakey.
God?
Now you put all these bullets in my belly...
and I'm gonna find out why.
I'll just say it.
You don't have to stick your fingers in me.
Jesus, just ask sometimes.
Fine.
Really?
Hands in pockets.
Guy named Paradox.
He said he'd get me out of The Void.
All I know is he works for the TVA.
The TVA.
We had an agreement.
I don't think this guy cares.
He will.
Hey, people!
How much longer
before the Time Ripper is active?
We're running the final safety checks.
Okay. All right.
Thanks for all your hard work, Ralph.
- Take your time.
- Really?
No, you drooling boob!
No! We have company.
Cancel the safety checks.
We need to be live now!
I hate you so much.
No! Stop!
Piss off! You're too late.
- You're fuckin' done.
- Why was Thor crying?
How dare you!
No one comes back from The Void.
Tell that to Cassandra Nova.
Paradox.
We have a problem.
Well, you are doughier than
you looked in Pyro's head.
You tried to kill me.
I literally have no...
You come for the king,
you better kill the king.
Welcome to the skull fuck club, Paradox.
You know she doesn't wash that hand.
What's this?
A Time Ripper?
- Naughty boy.
- Oh, no. We're on it.
We're gonna head down
and dismantle that thing now.
We got ya, boo.
You just keep playing those keys.
I don't want to destroy it.
I want to use it.
Now, shoo.
Mummy and Daddy are having a conversation.
You know, the funny thing is...
I was happy in The Void.
You sent your trash to me.
Alioth and I cleaned it up.
Everyone was happy.
And then you had to go
and piss on my side of the fence.
And so now the fence must come down.
I'm going to use your little Time Ripper.
And I'm going to destroy this universe...
and the next and the next and the next...
until all that's left is The Void.
And I get to play God.
Come on.
Now you're going to show me how
to use this fancy gadget of yours.
And don't worry, I've called some friends
to make sure we're not disturbed.
Sorry to bother, madam,
but there's something you need to see.
We're getting indications of an unsanctioned
Time Ripper activating on Earth-10005.
Whose district is that?
Paradox.
Well, thank you so much
for your help, darling.
God. Good to get out of that head.
What a mess!
Stop!
Let's give it a beat for the extras to clear.
Go, go, go!
Oh, my God!
- Oh. My. God.
- Fuck.
It's her!
Come on, girl!
That's my girl!
We don't have to be apart ever, ever again.
Never, ever...
- Sorry!
- Fuck!
What's Café Gratitude doing here?
Sorry about that.
Tremble not, sweet Mary Puppins.
I'll handle him.
Come here, girl.
Papa's here.
Hey, do not insult
this animal's autonomy.
She can decide who her papa is.
What's it gonna be, girl, huh?
Original recipe or Van Milder here?
That's funny.
I can gently tap the fourth wall too.
The Proposal.
The fuck was that?
- Bitch, you think that's what I do?
- Both of you shut up.
You smell somethin'?
Yeah, you.
A lot of you.
Told you there were
a lot of Deadpools over there.
That's bad.
I take it they're not friendly.
Goodness, no.
Sorry about this, boys.
Mission over.
Cause of death,
one hundred kill-thirsty Deadpools.
They're dumb.
But they can fight.
Not me, though.
Would love to get in the mix
but I have low bone density...
and I have to keep my face safe.
- Hold, please.
- Oh, God.
All right. Look.
Guys!
Deadpool Prime here.
- Our fight isn't with you...
- Hey!
When I want your opinion,
I'll take Wolverine's dick out of your mouth.
That's Kidpool.
She's the dirtiest.
Can we just be done?
We're just getting started.
No, no, no. With the whole multiverse thing.
It's not great.
It's just been miss...
after miss...
after miss.
Look, The Wizard of Oz
did the multiverse first...
and they did it best.
The gays knew it.
But we didn't listen.
Let's just take the L and move on.
I think it's been steadily great
since Endgame.
What are you talking about?
The multiverse is over.
Cassandy gonna destroy
the fuck outta every timeline.
- Y'all can't do shit about it.
- Do you not get it?
If we don't go down to the subway
and stop her, we all die.
Say, the boss lady don't want
no disturbances.
You wanna get down to the subway,
you gotta go through us.
Uzi time, baby.
Look alive!
- I think I'm hit.
- No shit.
You did that on purpose.
I did no such thing!
Listen to me, gorgeous.
How long does it take for you to regenerate?
Regenerate?
You really are God's perfect idiot,
aren't you?
- I'm okay.
- How dare you!
You insensitive son of a bitch!
How was I supposed to know
he doesn't regenerate?
I'm not a medicine woman.
Look. A donut cart.
- They're practically hospitals.
- What?
- They sell portable triage units.
- They don't.
- I'm gonna get you to safety.
- He's not.
Deep breath.
Hey, why are we stopping?
I'm just catching my breath.
What, are your legs on vacation?
You're dead weight!
That's because I'm paralyzed.
We all have problems.
Listen to me.
You're gonna live.
Look at me, Nicepool.
Say it!
I'm gonna live.
Say it with me.
You're gonna live.
I'm gonna live!
Say it louder!
I'm gonna live...
Hold your fire!
Sweet little puppy.
God damn it!
I don't think he's gonna make it.
God, he loved his face.
I can taste his final thought.
He was so afraid.
But he died a hero.
He died from murder, you dumb fuck.
And all I have to remember him by...
are these two gold-plated,
...50 caliber Desert Eagle pistoleros.
This is for him.
Are you ready?
I get to kill a hundred yous?
Fuck yeah, I'm ready.
Hey, you don't want to see this, bub.
That's a good girl.
Holy shit.
You save the good stuff
for special occasions?
Killing mostly.
What's the wind resistance
on those blowjob handles?
I'm sorry.
I'm just a catty bitch when I'm jealous.
All right, let's do this.
Maximum effort.
You're dead.
Motherfucker.
I wish I were deaf.
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
I don't wanna...
Come on.
I blew it.
After all that, the only thing
they're gonna remember...
is that God awful dismount!
What you laughing at,
you little fucker?
Uh-oh.
I guess these ones regenerate.
Come on. We don't have time for this.
Deadpools!
Stand down.
This Deadpool's with me.
Oh, no.
Holy shit.
That's fuckin' Peter!
Wait, you...
You guys know Peter?
You kidding me? Every Deadpool has a Peter.
Shit. Peter's a goddamn legend
in every Deadpool's world.
Peter-san.
Peter. Peter. Peter.
Enjoy my Peter.
Oh, now you're here.
Oh, well, you're too late. It's all over.
Not yet, it's not.
Whoa. No, no, no. We're very close.
Homestretch, folks. Promise.
Quick, let's up the stakes.
If she steals the Time Ripper's energy...
she has the power to
shred the fabric of all realities...
until there is nothing left but The Void.
How do we shut it down?
I don't know.
How about now?
The mask is really intimidating, huh?
It's like Batman,
except he can move his neck.
Okay, look, look, look.
The Ripper is fed from
a secure chamber below ground.
It is powered by twin matter and anti-matter
feeds converging inside the device.
Now, Cassandra Nova...
is redirecting the Ripper's power
to eliminate all timelines...
starting with this one.
Theoretically, you could stop her...
by short-circuiting the feeds
in the chamber below.
One of you were to create a
circuit between the two feeds...
then the released power
would destroy the machine.
- But, well, but...
- Come on, man.
If you're not gonna swallow, spit it out.
Whoever formed the bridge
would be annihilated.
- I could live with that.
- Yeah, I could live with that, too, actually.
You know, we survive anything.
We're like cockroaches.
Not this time.
This is matter and anti-matter.
They do not play nicely with each other.
When they mix in your body
you will be atomized.
Trust the laws of physics
if you don't trust me.
Even if you lived long enough to
make the circuit...
you will die down there.
Hold off. Hold.
You heard that asshole upstairs.
Even if we pull this off,
we're dead. Permanently.
That's why it's got to be me.
What?
Look, man...
you didn't ask for any of this.
You were right.
I lied.
I lied right to your face...
just to get you to help me. And you did.
You didn't lie.
You made an educated wish.
Come on.
You got a whole world to go back to.
I got nothin'.
Give me this.
Hey.
I waited a long time for this team up.
You know something?
You were the best Wolverine.
Say hi to your friends for me.
No!
Open the door!
I can't hear you over all the
noble sacrifice.
Why are you fucking doing this?
Because I'm Marvel Jesus.
Or Spock.
Hard to say.
Wade!
You fucking idiot!
Sorry, I'm just stalling.
I think I'm nervous about dying.
This should be me.
Say hi to my friends for me, peanut.
Wade!
You want to be an annoying prick,
do it this side!
You're gonna die in there,
you dumb fuck!
Hey! You don't need to do this.
I'm not doing it 'cause I need it.
I'm doing it because they do.
No!
He's not gonna make it.
It's over.
The Wolverine.
He's a hero in my world.
Whoever you think I am,
you got the wrong guy.
You were always the wrong guy...
till you weren't.
Wade.
Wade. You can finally, finally, matter.
Vanessa.
I wanna see Vanessa.
For the first time in my life,
I am proud to wear this suit.
It means I'm an X-Man.
I am the X-Man.
Paradox.
You've been busy.
Well, somebody had to be.
We had some
strange readings from this location.
You wouldn't know anything about an
unsanctioned Time Ripper, would you?
No. No. I wouldn't know anything about an
unsanctioned Time Ripper.
Maybe you should ask Cassandra Nova.
Because I was assured...
that she was safely held in The Void.
But no...
she was here.
And she fondled my brain.
How did you let this happen?
You weren't involved at all?
In stopping her, yes!
Yes. I was.
But, not nearly enough.
Not as much as the men
who went down there after her.
My men.
My friends.
I warned them.
That they would be completely obliterated
if they went. But they went anyway. Like...
Like heroes.
Because that's who they were.
They just did what they had to do.
With no concern for their own safety.
The fact that we are all still standing here
is a testament to their heroism.
Anyway, there's nothing you or I can do
to bring them back now.
He has risen, baby girl.
Fuck!
Found your new Anchor Being.
And we're doing just fine, you piece of shit.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Fine indeed.
All right. Put your greasy tits away,
you preening slut.
I don't understand.
How are you two still alive?
You were right.
One of us would have been killed.
But you put
a Deadpool and a Wolverine together...
make 'em hold hands
while listening to Madonna...
indestructible, motherfucker.
Let's get this Deadpool Variant
back to The Void.
- Wait, hold on. What?
- Nope. Actually...
This one's homegrown, like me.
He belongs here.
And you are?
Peterpool. But you can call me Peter.
And I hope that you do.
What the fuck is happening here?
You are under judgment...
for operating an unsanctioned Time Ripper.
- Take him.
- I was just doing what...
you don't have the guts to do.
Get your insolent hands off me!
Get off!
I'm grateful, gentlemen.
Let's hold the bows.
You led an
Omega-level mutant to this timeline.
- You're welcome.
- And you...
- shouldn't even be near this timeline.
- He's welcome.
And you look damn good in that suit.
I'm so sorry.
I wanna show you something.
Something huge.
That's what Scoutmaster Kevin used to say.
Do you see that?
Your universe is regenerating.
Whatever you did here...
you not only saved your world.
You spared your timeline from extinction.
I'd rest up.
I have a feeling your work
is only just getting started.
Till you're 90.
Wait!
We couldn't have made it out of The Void
without some help...
from some people that the world
kind of forgot.
Is there any way that you could maybe find
a way to bring them home?
I'll see what I can do.
And I promised my friend here...
that the TVA could undo some
pretty awful shit in his timeline.
What would you say to that?
Change the past?
Well, he did help me save the world.
And his past made him the man who did it.
There's nothing to fix, Mr. Wilson.
Logan.
Shawarma?
- I could eat.
- Yeah.
You know, the Avengers discovered shawarma.
They'd be lucky to have you.
- Oh.
- Oh, come on.
Fuck off!
Come here, my little cunchkin.
Yes, it's you. You're a survivor.
Oh, all is right in the world.
Yes, it is.
So what are you gonna do next?
I'll figure it out. I always do.
All right.
So I'll probably see you around?
Probably not.
See you, bub.
Logan.
Al. I'm back.
About damn time.
You holdin'?
I'm all outta devil's dandruff...
- and I'm shaking like an angry vibrator.
- Thank you, Al.
We have company.
Althea, this is...
This is Logan.
Nice to meet you, Logan.
Nice to meet you, too.
And this little ancient anal shit-knot is
Mary Puppins.
Or as I like to call her, Dogpool.
You want to treat yourself
to a little stroke?
- Get the tongue. There it is.
- Oh, my God! Motherfucker!
Right? It's like an armadillo
fucked a gremlin, angrily...
in a bed of gonorrhea...
- Wow.
- ...and didn't stop till the sun came up.
Everyone wants to matter.
Turns out that
you don't need to be Marvel Jesus to do it.
You just need to
open your eyes and look around.
And if you're lucky...
you'll find a few friends.
Old friends...
and some new ones too.
Give me the fucking dog. Talk to the girl.
Well, hi.
Hi.
You've been busy.
I did it for you.
And even if you don't want me,
It turns out...
I am the world-saving type.
Just look around this table
if you want proof.
And the best part?
Sometimes the people we save...
well, they save us right back.
You're not the only one with gifts.
What is this place?
Nice suit.
Zip it, Stan Lee.
I really like the,
the art in the Deadpool comics.
You know, I just always felt a
kind of a kinship to him.
And I just thought,
I'd like to play that guy someday.
I was there for three weeks
before I shot a single thing.
At our first day of shooting...
I was so nervous, man.
Everyone was sort of going,
"Who's this guy?"
You know, there was a lot of that and...
you know, "Is he gonna deliver or not?"
You can feel all that kind of pressure.
It's always the suit's fault.
Never the actor.
- This is...
- The only way.
So this is what it feels like.
And there's the lights.
For medical research.
- Bye-bye, video.
- Bye.
I'm tired of these absolutely vile rumors
that I got Johnny killed.
Let's look at the tape.
In The Void...
you're either food for Alioth...
or you work for her.
Go on, Johnny.
And I'll tell you who "her" is.
Cassandra Nova.
A megalomaniacal, psychotic asshole.
A finger licking dead-inside pixie slab of
third rate dime-store nut-milk.
- And I'll tell you what she can do.
- I'm listening.
She can lick my goddamn cinnamon ring clean
and kick rocks all the way to bald hell.
In fact, I don't give a shit if she removes
all my skin and...
pops me like some nightmarish blood balloon.
If the last thing I do in this godforsaken
cum-gutter existence...
is light that fuck-box on fire,
I still won't die happy.
Holy shit, girl. You crazy.
That's right, Wade.
I won't be happy until...
I've urinated on her freshly barbecued corpse
and husk-fucked the charred remains...
while gargling Juggernaut's juggernuts.
- Wow!
- And you can quote me.
'Kay.
Got you, fuckface.